♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday, A.D ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him
cheesing movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end la-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot it's cool called
Cambot, pan left ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Hi, girl ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ What a cool guy ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
♪ Wise cracker ♪
♪ You're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3,000 ♪
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] 30 seconds
to commercial science.
- Hey everybody, welcome
to the satellite of love.
My name is Joel and I'm
marooning out of space,
and I guess in a
way you are too.
I'm expecting a call from
the evil overlord scientists
who shot me into
space pretty soon.
- [Announcer] Commercial
science in 15 seconds.
- So stick around, we're gonna
find out what the movie is,
and then we're gonna have
an invention exchange,
and then we can get on
with the experiment.
And then after that,
I guess you could get
on with your lives.
- [Announcer] Commercial science
in five, four, three, two,
commercial science now.
- Don't go away,
we'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
Okay now, just take it easy,
this isn't gonna hurt a bit.
- Oh, it's gonna
hurt, it's gonna hurt.
- Always be careful when
Joel is using the laser tool,
it's all right?
- Ooh.
- See, okay look, I'm done.
I'm done already, I'm done.
Here okay, jump down
here is your RAM chip,
come on there you go,
get out of here now.
Oh, my evil overlords are
calling me, come in sirs.
- Come in Joel in you
pusillanimous poltroon.
- Hey sirs, what's
going on, what's up?
- Well, what's up every
week at this time,
you anti-gravitational
sewage leak.
- It's the invention exchange,
and this time we've got
a real winner for you.
Something that'll sure to
please all of your frat buddies.
- It's a little
something we like to call
the mechanically-inflating
whoopee cushion.
As we all know the
whoopee cushion
has been a longstanding favorite
among pranksters
around the world.
(laughs)
- Yes, this one's got
a little twist though.
It's a self-inflating model
and it's filled with
real methane gas.
- Get the the picture?
- Larry.
- Ready.
(cushion inflates)
- Whoooh, oh, (chuckles).
- Excuse me.
(laughs)
What do you think?
- I'm shocked, it's
really sophomoric.
- Thank you.
Wow, what's your
little contribution
to science this week,
Joelita, my little
vacuum flower?
(both laughs)
- Okay sirs, well this
is my new invention,
it's called the
Cambot bubble button.
It's something you wear it
when you want to make
a big impression,
let's say it's your first
day of school somewhere,
or you're going in
for a job interview.
Just put on the
Cambot bubble button,
and you're on an automatic
disco dance party.
(cambot engine roars)
Hit the music Cambot.
(upbeat music)
You see.
Okay stop it, I got a joke.
(cambot engine roars)
You know what champagne
goes right me.
(Tom and Crow laugh)
Anyway, what do you think sirs?
- Oh, very amusing.
- Ooh!
- Anyway, your film
today is "Robot Monster".
It's a classic film
that was nominated
for a Golden Turkey Award
for being one of the
foulest films ever.
(laughs)
- See to call this film wretched
would just be an insult
to the word wretched.
It stars no one.
Oh man, you won't believe this.
- Yes and to further
your viewing displeasure,
we have a double dose of that
classic Commando Cody serial,
"Radar Men From The Moon".
Deal with it Pete boy.
- Enjoy.
(alarm buzzes)
- Oh, movies time.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] I don't know,
I thought that invention
was a good idea.
- [Crow] Flaming whoopee
cushion, that was brilliant.
- [Joel] No, not that
mine, bubbles thing.
- [Tom] Oh yeah, I like bubbles.
- [Crow] Look at this,
another one of these,
"Radar Men From The Moon."
- [Tom] Seen it.
Can we go?
- [Tom] Done it.
- [Crow] Starring the same
people as the week before,
the week before that, an
episode after episode.
- [Joel] What did you do today?
Well, we watched a stupid movie.
Same as always, another
day in the South mine.
- [Joel] Well, try to
keep a good attitude,
we got to do two of these.
- [Tom] What?
Oh brother.
- [Joel] I don't
think I can do that.
(dramatic music)
Yeah, we know, we know.
- [Tom] Music's good this time.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Flight to destruction,
ooh, I'm quivering in my chair.
Commander Cody purses Daly and
Graber who on Krog's orders
attempt to bomb the Rocketship
with Cody and the
kidnappers (mumbles).
- [Joel] Okay guys, see if
you can spot the escape scene
that happens, we always seem
to miss it when they get out
just before something explodes.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] I remember correctly,
they're turning onto
the bridge of death.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Hey, here comes Cody
and he's got his
bear goggles on.
- [Crow] He's trash, and now
he's going to get bombed.
(Tom laughs)
Mm-hmm.
(dramatic music)
Oh, look, it's a bomb.
- [Joel] Hey, that scene
wasn't in last time.
- [Tom] That's 'cause they
didn't get the film back
from the drug store yet.
- [Crow] Upon further review,
the revs find that
that Cody is dead.
The play stands, Cody is dead.
- So the people on the moon
are planning a direct
attack on the world
as soon as their sabotages
have softened up our defenses.
- Do you think the
jentors are of succeeding?
- You've seen what the Reagans
have already done here.
If they send out a
fleet of Rocketships,
armed with atomic
weapons like those,
or perhaps even larger ones,
it wouldn't be difficult
to hold out against them.
- I'd say our best move would be
to attempt an
attack on the moon.
- We'd be at a
terrific disadvantage.
I don't even see how it
could land ships there
and face the Reagans.
- We just can't sit here
and wait to be attacked.
- [Crow] Sure can, we've
done it a million times.
- Reddick, the ruler told
me they planned to attack
after their saboteurs here have
accomplished their mission.
If we could round up
the gang operating here,
we may stave off the attack
until we are better
prepared to meet it.
- Yes--
- [Crow] (mumbles) is
uglier than mud fence.
- You know some of the
saboteurs, don't you?
- [Crow] You make a train
to get dough rolled.
- And my flying suit gives
me a considerable advantage
in running them down.
- Right.
I'll have you notified whenever
there's another attack.
In the mean time, we'll
put every available man
on this case.
Goodbye Cody.
- Goodbye, sir.
- Bye.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] What a nice guy.
- [Joel] He seems like
a nice enough fellow.
- [Tom] At first.
- Hey, forget about
the Pearl then like,
just screw it back together.
- In a short time now,
so you arrange to get
another truck to mount it in.
- Okay, but I'll
need some more money.
- [Crow] My purse is
on the counter, honey.
- Let's sell some
more of those jewels
you brought down from the moon.
- I have only a few of them
left and it must keep those
for an emergency.
- [Joel] What's he going to do,
(indistinct) in that outfit?
- Your career of bank robbery.
- Not me, I'm already
on parole for that.
- I know, but you would
be wise to continue
to obey my orders, your
more recent activities
would be of extreme
interest to the authorities.
- [Tom] Oh, who's
going to report me?
You Mr. Moon man.
(dramatic music)
- Do you need
someone to help you?
- Yeah, they'll have
to do the dirty work.
- [Tom] Dirty work, yeah.
- Of course, I'll go
on to check on them.
- Very well, make your
arrangements at once.
Select the bank
which is located in
a not-too heavily
patrolled area.
- [Tom] Like Yellowstone?
Oh, that guy's good at leaning.
(siren blaring)
Hey, his face rings a bell.
- [Joel] An M.P.A system bell.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Motion
Picture Association?
- [Joel] It's possible.
(dramatic music)
- Here they come.
(bullet rattles)
- [Joel] Oh, what a time
to get a kink in the back.
You got one too,
heartbreak of psoriasis.
(dramatic music)
Hey, you could get in,
there're seats for that.
- [Crow] Maybe he thinks
it's a skateboard.
- [Tom] It's a running
board, not a riding board.
- They're losing out,
we're out of traffic.
- [Joel] Hey, this isn't
the way to taco John's.
- [Crow] Whatever you
do, don't open your door.
- [Tom] Oh, alone,
you're the man for me.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Gomez, I'm not
your new best friend.
Ooh, lucky one.
- [Tom] Nice throw.
- [Crow] Oops!
Hey, it's John Cleese.
- That we must have more money,
you've got to get it somehow.
- Not by any more bank jobs--
- [Joel] Krog is
not looking good.
- We'll have to figure
out something else.
- I'll radio the moon,
perhaps, Reddick can advice us.
- [Joel] Good idea, maybe I'll
send you some moon or some...
- [Tom] He better
get some Shaddai.
- Krog calling Reddick.
- Meanwhile, back
at Caesar's palace.
- [Krog] Krog calling Reddick.
- [Tom] Don't ever interrupt me
while I'm playing
the nickel slots.
- [Krog] Krog calling Reddick.
- [Joel] And stop
talking into a pine corn.
- I have to report that our
scheme for obtaining money
was a failure.
- [Tom] Some day it'll grow
and he'll be
talking into a tree.
- Can you suggest some plan
that might be more successful?
- I think I can, from what I
hear of activities on earth,
kidnapping important persons
and holding them for ransom,
has proved highly profitable.
- It's very trendy.
- Commando Cody who flew
his Rocketship to the moon
is very valuable to the defense
organization of its country.
I suggest you select him.
- An excellent idea, we
shall carry it out at once.
- [Tom] That's
why he's the boss.
- (mumbles) and a lot safer
than robbing another bank.
- Of course, Commando
Cody should be worth
at least $100,000.
- Oh, at least.
- Shall we bring them here?
- No.
Hire a plane, take him to,
- Paradise city?
Oh, not another lab fight.
- [Tom] Hey, this bra
is coming along nicely.
- [Tom and Crow] Oh, I hate
to shoot a butt like that.
- I love that.
(dramatic music)
- Where's Cody?
- Right over there.
- [Crow] Ooh.
- [Tom] Oh, it works
every time, (laughs).
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Yeah, well,
that's for Enrico, for me.
- [Tom] It is a good thing
scientists can really fight.
They must have been
taking classes.
- [Crow] Loose stool.
- [Tom] If I told you once,
I told you a thousand times,
we're not rounding
off Pi to four.
- [Joel] You were my tea guys,
think you're pretty tough.
And that's for Madame Curie.
She's so cute when
she's passed out.
- [Crow] Throw them out.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] All right,
the test tubes.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] What's the physics
of a broken jar, college boy?
Are you referring to the
mandible or the maxilla?
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Yeah, tell your
friends, Crick and Watson.
- [Crow] I've got a
headache this big.
- [Joel] Oh, dropped
him like a bad habit.
(dramatic music)
- Now will you tell
us where Cody is?
- [Joel] In Wyoming.
- I don't know.
- Why don't we grab her
and use her to trap Cody?
- [Joel] I am grabbing her.
- Good idea, find
your way sister.
Wait a minute.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] At least she got
to bring her clutch purse.
- [Crow] I think it's
alligator, it's very nice,
Very stylish.
(car engine roars)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Is she
double dating again?
Well, they seem like
nice enough fellows.
- [Crow and Tom] At first.
- [Tom] How many times
do I have to tell them,
no kickball in the lab?
- Well, say to men who
wrecked the raygun,
they came after you.
- Where's Jonah?
- I don't know, maybe
they took her with them.
Two men and a woman drove away
from here, just as I came in.
They were too far
away to be recognized,
but it must've been them.
- [Joel] They have Jonah,
they're taking her
to the San Diego zoo.
- Police headquarters.
- [Joel] Calling all
cars, calling all cars,
be on the lookout for
two man in a babe.
Maybe I'm with a gigantic
experimental brazier here.
You know what to do, strap
it on and parade around
singing show tunes.
- [Crow] (sneezes),
last year, whoa, Zaunt.
- [Joel] You're not
supposed to do that.
- [Crow] That stirred
up my RAMs real bad.
- Okay, I'll tell him.
The police found out
that the car went
to the East side airport and
a man took off with Jonah
in a trotted plane, they
left just a few minutes ago.
- I'll be lucky if I'm
lucky I can catch them.
- [Tom] What about the bra?
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Window.
- [Crow] Window, window, hey.
Jack-O-lantern private dog.
- [Joel] Nipple
nipple twin Creek.
- [Tom And Crow] Fly!
(dramatic music)
- Can I offer you some peanuts?
- [Crow] I hope they show
this movie in that flight.
(plane engine roars)
- So do you like
my plane, honey?
- [Crow] Here I come
to save the dame.
Oh, he sees them.
(dramatic music)
- Don't get excited sister,
I'll take car of him.
- [Joel] Wow, he can fly
and shoot at the same time,
he must be ambidextrous.
- [Tom] Well, I give my
right arm to be ambidextrous.
(bullet rattles)
- oh.
She seems cute when
she's knocked out.
- [Crow] Oh, Cody shooting.
Wasn't there something in
the rule book about equal
and opposite reactions, Joel?
(plane engine roars)
- [Tom] Done.
- Aurgh, that's hot new.
- [Joel] Commando Surprano.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh, steering's
out, saves weight.
Oh, nice dive.
- [Tom] He ditched her.
- [Crow] Just like Karen Black.
- [Joel] Where's Charlton
Heston when you need him?
- [Crow] And they should
really work on this act
for air shows, it would
really fly, (laughs).
- [Crow] Hi honey,
come die with me.
- [Tom] Hey, de
plane, de plane, boss.
- He wrecked the controls.
- [Tom] Why don't you put it
down over there by those rocks?
(dramatic music)
(plane crushes)
- [Joel] Bang.
You have to wait till next week.
- [Crow] Nice parking.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] This is great,
back-to-back thrills.
- [Tom] Yeah.
Try to cope with it you guys.
- [Crow] Hey, it's
a new character.
- [Joel] No, it's the
same old character.
- [Tom] It said new.
- [Joel] Just think of it as
was getting a booster shot
twice in the same day
by the same doctor.
- [Tom] Yeah, Dr. Mengele.
- All right.
- [Crow] Isn't the Geneva
Convention have rules
against this sort of thing?
- [Crow] You know I think
I'm going to go cut
an Apple in half
and watch it brown.
- [Tom] I think I'll go worse.
- [Tom] Hey servo,
let's ditch him.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Joel] Oh, you guys come on,
cut that out, get back here.
- [Crow] You can't make me.
You can't make me,
you can't make me.
- I'm hiding.
- Come on, out.
- [Joel] Come Servo, stop it.
Come back here--
- You can't make,
you can't make.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] This is Buddhists,
you create us to suffer.
- [Joel] Oh, get back over here.
- [Crow] Commando
Cody' flying suit,
blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
- [Joel] I'm surrounded by
idiots of my own design.
(dramatic music)
(plane engine roars)
- [Tom] Good bye pretty lady,
enjoy your inflight meal,
baked in Alaska, (laughs).
(dramatic music)
Yeah, they should
work on an air show.
- [Crow] Psych.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Tom] Nice climbing.
- He wrecked the control.
- Whoa!
- Get into that parachute.
- [Joel] Parachute, there was
no parachute in the last real.
- [Crow] Look at that, it
looks like the little ladies
have the time of her life.
- [Tom] Shoot.
(plane crashes)
Oh, well, there goes the model,
what about the real plane?
- [Crow] I'm beginning to
think these endings are rigged.
- [Joel] Oh, that
was worse than usual.
- [Tom] I got her, I got
her come to papa, whoops.
- [Tom] Hey, this
is fun, watch this,
Weeh, wah-weeh, (laughs).
It's like a big balloon.
- What became of that, man?
- He must have landed
somewhere near here.
If you're sure you're all
right, I'll look for him.
- Oh, of course I am, I
walk over to the road.
- Okay.
- [Joel] Okay, let me just,
okay, yeah that's right.
Nipple, nipple and fly.
What a fantastic man!
It's been a good day,
I better head towards
the highway now.
Where is that
highway, where am I?
- [Tom] You think you'd
have it inflated ego?
- [Crow] Or at least
in-flame tissue.
[Tom] Here's Chaz
wearing his Armani
from the Desert Wear Collection.
- [Joel] For goons on the go.
Hey, you call for a murder car.
- [Tom] No, thanks,
I already got one.
(dramatic music)
(car engine roars)
- [Joel] He's switching
to the light rock station.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] The Moon rock station.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Tom] He flies
better than Superman.
- The flight suit
chasing at us, step out.
- Uh, are you crazy?
- Don't argue, step out.
- [Joel] Oh, he could
have never have known,
he was picking up a
moon goon, poor guy.
- [Joel] Right,
right, shoot him,
that's your solution
to everything.
Something gets in your way,
you pull out your little gun
and you got to shoot
them, well listen, Mr,
someday, there's going to be
a flying Rocketeer behind you
who's going to shoot back.
(bullets rattle)
Whoa!
- [Tom] Hey yo, winged him.
[Crow] Better get out the dogs.
- I've stopped him.
- [Joel] What's the limit
on Cody's this year anyway?
- [Tom] When you shoot down
a Cody, do you call a ranger
or do you call an air
traffic controller?
- [Crow] It's a gutting
them, that's the hard part.
Oh darn, I just got this
back from the garage.
Meanwhile, back in the
bowels of the earth.
- I must report to the moon.
- [Crow] I think we all
reported to the moon
at one time or another.
- Krog calling Reddick.
(soft music)
- Reddick?
- Krog calling Reddick.
- [Tom] Reddick pickup line
one please, Mr. Reddick.
- [Joel] He's run a good way to.
- I have to report another
failure, your excellency.
We were unable to
capture Commando Cody
and hold him for ransom.
- You still have no funds?
- No Sir.
- [Tom] Apply for
earth's grant quick.
we are unable to
continue our campaign
against earth's defenses.
- Listen carefully, Krog.
I cannot have my preparations
for invading the earth
delayed by such a minor detail,
obtaining a small
amount of money.
If the men you now have
cannot accomplish this simple
mission, then hire someone
who can produce results.
This is an order.
- I understand your excellency.
- [Joel] Hmm, hire someone else.
I wonder if Kelly has
a thug department.
- You heard, it's up to you to
decide whether you can still
be useful to us or...
- [Joel] Oh, I forgot my line.
We'll figure out something,
if we could only use our arms.
- A little job, Duke was
trying to get you in on it.
- Maybe he'll still
go through with it.
Well it's risky,
but it might work.
It's the Western
wholesale supply company.
They keep their payroll
in the office safe
every Friday night.
There's a man in the office.
- [Joel] Every time he
talks, the scene fades out.
Meanwhile, further
along in the script.
(alarm blaring)
No one's been shot yet,
it's going pretty well.
- [Tom] I think they got that
car and get away rentals.
(car engine roars)
- It's the cops, get going.
- [Tom] Be on the lookout
for a 1935 murder car,
smart Looker priced to move.
You'll be the head
of your neighborhood,
owned by a little old
lady, 1935 Porter,
that's my mother, dear, helps
me through everything I do,
and I'm so glad she's here.
- [Joel] That's a
stunning Jerry Van Dyke.
Jerry Van Dyke has a
bumper sticker that says,
"My other car is my mother."
- [Crow] Oh, he's a nut.
(tires screaking)
You are watching the
all car chase network.
All cars, all
chases all the time.
(soft music)
(bullet rattles)
- They're getting closer.
- [Joel] Shoot, shoot,
shoot, it's everyone's answer
to everything in this film.
- [Tom] Hey, that's my lunch.
(Car engines roaring)
(bullet rattling)
- [Joel] Wow, it
was a nice shot.
I suppose he tried to do that.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Meanwhile, back
at the Cody Institute
for a scientist to get pummeled.
- Honey, I'm home.
- Finally got a break.
- They called me down to
the jail hospital to see
if I could identify a prisoner,
and he turned out to be one
of those two who'd been
making all the trouble for us.
- Well, how did they catch him?
- Well, he and another man
stage in the payroll robbery,
the police went after
them and the car crashed.
The other man was killed,
but our power was only
banged up with him.
- [Joel] See board up
there and the guys,
he was a banged up a little.
- Hey cool.
- [Joel] I got this giant dart.
- [Tom] Don't do it Joel,
you'll ruin the screen.
No, don't.
- People around
the jail hospital--
- [Joel] I don't
care, just an idea.
- We might be able to hurt.
- But aren't they going to
try to find out something?
- Yes, they're going
to move him under guard
to a private Sanitarium
where we can question him
without any danger of
the story linking out,
and throwing the whole
country into a panic.
- When will that be?
- Probably this afternoon,
Henderson was going to let
me know as soon as they make
arrangements for
having him transferred.
I'd like you to go with me Ted.
- Sure.
- Great,
if I stay around here, I'll
get my butt kicked again.
- I got some news about Graybar.
A friend of mine is a
trustee in the jail hospital,
and he tipped me off,
they're moving Graybar out
in an ambulance this afternoon.
- My trustee friend.
- Anything we can do about it?
- Yeah, I got it
all figured out.
Now my friend told me which
road the ambulance is taking.
- [Tom] Stay down.
- [Joel] What a party!
I was so hammered.
(dramatic music)
Look guys, it's a road kill.
- [Crow] Huh?
All right, give me a snow
cone and two bomb pipes.
- Start walking across
the country, run.
- [Tom] I'm wearing
white though, that's
a very good humor.
- Cheese.
(dramatic music)
(bullet rattles)
That's gotta hurt.
- What about the driver?
- I sent him hiking.
You should've slugged him,
as soon as he gets to jail,
he'll have the
cops on our trail.
- Oh, that's okay, there's
a car parked a few miles
up the road to pick you up.
- Okay, let's go.
- [Tom] Wow, now they can
have all the frozen treats
they ever wanted.
- [Joel] That's all haul.
(car engine roars)
Cool car, that's
a cool Cody car.
- [Tom] Hey, wait a minute,
there's no ice cream
on these sticks.
- [Crow] Those are
tongue depressors,
this is an ambulance you idiot.
- Oh.
- It's about time you got here,
the cops are on their way.
- What!
- Yeah, it's coming over
the radio right now.
- [Tom] But check local
listings in your area.
- [Cop] Calling all
cars, calling all cars
the stolen ambulance was
ordered turning on to the
East end of Harrison
Canyon highway.
- I told her you should
have slugged that driver.
- [Cody] Calling
police headquarters,
calling police headquarters.
- It's Cody.
- [Police] Police
headquarters, I'm in.
- [Cody] This is Commando Cody,
I picked up your broadcast
and I'm just turning into the
West end of Harrison, Kenya--
- You think that's
an honorary title?
- I'll stop it for you.
- You'll get some man
up there soon as we can.
- It's a bad break,
what's he doing out here?
- Probably on his way
to third degree me.
I'll go back to
Todd with you, Sam.
You'll keep going with
the ambulance until
you can ditch it.
If you meet Cody
first smash him.
- Right.
- [Joel] Man, he should
just get some counseling.
He wouldn't want to smash
people all the time.
- [Crow] Smash,
slug, shoot, walk,
it's all the same to him,
I mean just wasn't beat up
at all as I was a kid.
(car engine roars)
- [Crow] We now return you
to the all car chase network
already in progress.
- You think we'll
meet them on the road?
- [Tom] Well, if I
wrote my script right,
we should be meeting
him pretty soon.
- [Joel] Tell you guys how
about how James Dean died?
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] When I tell
you, there is page 92.
- [Joel] Nah, we've done
this a million times.
We gotta get outta here.
(dramatic music)
- Okay, let's see if what
we just saw in the movie
could really happen,
the airplane leaves
Krog's cave at 4:00 PM, it
flies due North, Tom servo,
what's the estimated speed of
a two-person-single
engine plane?
- Let's see a assuming a tail
window of 30 miles per hour,
and figuring an average
weight of 135 pounds
for each passenger, I'd say
123 knots plus or minus 3%
for the drag coefficient.
- Are you compensating for
a positive Doppler shift?
- Of course, I am.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay, so it's 130 knots,
how fast would commando Cody
have to fly to catch
up to the plane, Crow?
- Easy, Commando Cody would
need to rev up his Rocket pack
to 290 nights for 18 minutes.
Of course, gentlemen,
we're only theorizing here.
In reality, it takes only
one film edit to advance Cody
to the plane, (laughs).
- Right, it is just a serial
anyway, the whole thing ends
in a fiery plane crash anyway.
- Oh.
- Oh,
- Like that.
- Very nice.
- Well, as long as we're talking
about reality here though,
let's talk about that
pumpkin head for a second.
Even a ninth grader could see
that with all the heaviness
and position of the
rockets on Cody's back,
he'd be cartwheeling his butt
all over Southern California.
- Right, but Tom, remember
it's just a serial,
it's only a show, this
couldn't really happen.
You know that thing
that Isaac Asimov said
about King Kong's
body being too huge,
it couldn't happen
physically, he'd crumble.
- Yeah, he also argued that
the incredible shrinking man
could never have been heard
because his vocal chords would
be so tiny, his voice
would be ultrasonic,
even dogs would have
to go, "What, huh?"
- But keep in mind gentlemen,
that physics has yet
to legitimize the existence
of Isaac Asimov sideburns.
- Oh yes we see,
it's exactly like the
invisible man paradox.
If he's truly invisible,
he'd be blind because his
retinas would be transparent.
- Well, I know one that's
even true in real life,
it's unbelievable, Physics has
yet to explain how bumblebees
fly, their bodies are too
big for their wingspan.
Physics says bumblebees
can't fly, but they fly.
Go figure Tom servo.
- Hmm, wingspan, body
weight, air resistance, whoa.
- Oh man, Crawl, any
thoughts on the subject?
- What was the question again?
- The thing about bumblebee.
- Oh, well sure, bumblebees
can't fly, big deal, so what.
- Oh man, I got to get
more memory in these guys.
Hey Cambot, what do
you think of that,
about bumblebees not
being able to apply?
(upbeat music)
- See you're as good as new.
- [Tom] Well, don't give
me any more brain teasers
and my head will blow up, I
thought that it was a rush
robot monster, Oh man.
- [Crow] True stereo,
three-dimension process,
sounds serious.
- [Joel] George Nader, that's
Ralph Nader's naughty brother.
He wrote safe at any speed.
- [Crow] Claudia Barrett
from the comedy team,
grin and Barrett.
- [Tom] Selena Royal,
what a great movie,
wasn't Woody Allen in that?
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] John Mylong
from the comedy team
of Mylong and winding road.
- [Crow] Gregory Moffett,
who went on to star
in "Yards of leather."
- [Tom] Pamela Paulson,
she's never made a bad film.
- [Joel] George Barrows, too
ashamed to show his own face.
(gentle wistful music)
- [Crow] The automatic
billion bubble machine,
is that expensive?
- [Joel] No, it's not the
machine that's expensive,
it's paying the guy
who counts the bubbles.
- [Crow] Elmer Bernstein.
(dramatic music)
Wyott Ordung,
- Wyott, yes.
(cat meows)
Stop torturing that cat.
- Am I dead?
- Are the disintegrated.
- Good, does that mean we can
play house now, you promise?
- [Crow] Is that the
billion-bubble machine Joel?
- [Joel] No, that's
the 50-bubble machine.
- These words are
full of spinsters,
it's either them or us, come on.
- [Crow] I'd rather it be you.
Hey, come on, let's go
play on the high cliffs.
- [Tom] Music by piano Saurus.
- [Crow] No, it's the
band that's called,
"Stop us if we get annoying."
- [Tom] I've seen this movie,
isn't this the boy of
the plastic bubble?
- [Crow] That's
the kid's disease,
he grows up to be John Travolta.
- [Tom] Oh no, that's so sad.
(mumbles)
- [Crow] Hey it's
Randolph Mantooth,
he played "Johnny Gage," right?
Brandon Park.
- If you insist, but come here,
- [Joel] Kids, don't ever
sit on an archeologist lab.
- We couldn't live
piece with each other?
- Okay, I'll be from
a friendly planet.
- Good, does that mean
you can play house now?
- No.
- I'm friendly but I
still have find out
what they're doing here.
- We, we are archeologists boy,
people will try to find out
what men were like, when they
could learn to read or write.
The only way to pass on you
got the new pictures like this.
- You see, our job is to chip
it out carefully and take it
to a museum so people can study.
- Oh, don't patronize
me rock jerky.
- It's even better
than being Cowboys.
- You bet, once he
has space in robot.
- As far as we know
that we had no spaceman
at those times and
Dropbox either.
- Are you like some of
those people I saw last time
I was on pluto?
(archeologists laugh)
I'll get the sudden Johnny.
- [Woman] Johnny!
- Oh Johnny, It looks like
you stirred a little outside
of your orbit, doesn't it?
- [Joel] You're in
trouble bubble boy.
- Here we're in the cage.
- What's the deal,
their houses are
right on the edge of a Canyon.
- Don't you like her?
- No doubt.
- Johnny that was--
- You kids promised you'd
take a nap right after lunch
if we took you on this
picnic and all to school.
- [Crow] I think his
head is problematic.
- Not at all Johnny, but
the camp I used to go to,
we used to have to
take a nap after lunch,
right up until we were 14.
- You did?
- You're terminally out of it.
- Will you be here
when I get back?
- If we are, you are
welcome to join us.
- [Crow] In our dance of death.
Nice family, how'd you like
to put them in a museum?
Little Mason jar
accent, real nice.
- [Tom] Hey, great, a picnic
at the slag heap, thanks Ma'am.
- There you are.
- Hey mom, tell us
about hell again here.
- Hey honey, take these
as best as turnover.
- He'd let me stay.
- I don't think
he would, Johnny.
- Say it, if we have a good
father around our house.
- I don't know dear,
would you like that?
- If we do, I'd be in a big
scientist to make Rocketships
and things like that.
- [Crow] And rocket candy.
- [Crow] And so after a
meal of crushed granite
and pipe racks, they slept.
(bells chiming)
Scientists finally realized
that the barren landscape
inspires a child's
natural curiosity.
(lightening rattles)
Oh, he's always been
light sensitive.
Dark.
- Oh.
- [Joel] Oh, the movie's been
attacked by a nature film.
- [Crow] It's gecko,
Roman wrestling, (laughs).
Alligator turnovers, all around.
Like dueling and handbags.
- [Joel] Looks like outtakes
from mutual of Omaha,
20 million BC.
- [Crow] Ah, I win.
Oh man, that
Schlitz malt liquor,
boy, do I have the Zach lace?
- [Joel] What is a Zack lace?
- Uh...
- That's all right.
Your pants got
shorter, look at that.
- Maybe he got taller.
What kind of universe is this,
where they alter your
clothing when you sleep?
- [Crow] It's an
alternating universe.
- [Joel] Jesus, it's a flasher,
you better get out of there.
(dramatic music)
This is what comes from
teaching apes sign language.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] At least they'll
be ready for heavy weather.
It kind of looks like your
uncle Lou from that picture,
you showed us.
- Hey.
- [Crow] Hey look,
they got asteroids.
- [Joel] Hey, they
must be pretty advanced
if they have Atari.
(soft music)
- [Crow] Cool.
- [Joel] Hmm, STS model rockets.
- [Crow] He comes from a
planet where they evolved
from apes and water coolers.
- [Joel] Home planets,
stop my milk delivery,
pick up my mail.
- Extension Roman, Xj2,
regarding their guidance Roman.
I salute you.
- You are late on 18 minutes.
- [Tom] The lights
were against me.
- Gravitational pull is
stronger than reporting.
Point seven, six, five,
two higher than our planet.
- Accepted, report.
- [Crow] He's so adorable.
- May I report for other news?
Master, no life has been
discovered on any other planets.
Earth is our only rival.
- That's great, thanks.
- [Tom] What's he
looking through?
- [Crow] A glass darkly.
- Has not mastered
the cosmic rate, wherever
I directed the counselor,
they crumbled, at first, the
fool was thought it came from
one of them to have any nations.
They began destroying each
other with hydrogens gas.
I announced myself to keep
them from fighting out cities,
which will give people
I'm not amusement.
- [Joel] Oh good, you saved six
flags and Disneyland, great.
- Truly, they battled against
me, their resistance patterns
showed something--
- [Crow] Is he
looking into a mirror?
It's like a sketch
a friend again.
- This guy (mumbles).
- Yeah.
- My pulse has been
reduced to plus zero, zero.
Reject, error, good, that's
great guidance, I approved it.
The energizer has has
scanned squared pit.
No life above that level exists.
- I come to think
there's more accurate.
(mumbles)
- Category,
there was error of 16 billion.
- Great one is never wrong.
And there are perhaps
eight people left on earth.
- Not perhaps, precisely.
Find and destroy them,
then report back.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] It's the Berlin wall.
- [Tom] No it's,
this is the future,
that's the great
wall of Cleveland.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Tom] I don't think
wiring was up to code.
Hey, did you get the stuff?
Come on in.
He's gotta build the sometimes.
- (mumbles) have a good mind
to give you a threshing.
Didn't we tell you
it never, never,
never to go outside of those
whys without our permission?
- Martha, anger won't keep the
boy from doing it the again,
you must tell him why, you
know that terrible things
that have happened when
the Roman landed on earth.
The only reason we're still
alive is that your sister,
Alice and I, worked out a way
to reflect these deadly beings
away from the house, he
can't see us, he hear us.
But one word spoken
outside the barrier,
and he would be down on us.
- [Crow] Like ugly on an eighth.
- Do you understand that Johnny?
- But I saw him.
- Saw who?
- Roman, he's in the cave
at the end of the ravine.
- Then he's found us out.
- Not yet,
we'd all be dead by now.
- I was in the cave
painting his picture
the way we saw him
on the viewer screen.
- Why were you
doing that, Johnny?
- So in case, he did
wipe out the human race,
there'd be some record
of how it happened.
- [Joel] Johnny, don't be hero,
don't be a fool with your life.
- Look to me like he's
making it his home.
- Why here, why so close?
- [Tom] It's near the mall.
(Johnny mumbles)
- No, Johnny, the army of the
entire world tried and failed.
We have thrown everything
we had done to him,
but he's in pelvis.
- Unless we can
find his weak spot.
- [Tom] Like his underwear line?
- Can I have just
a little water mom?
- [Joel] We have all the
advantages, we hold the power.
- Why here, why here?
- Perhaps we're the last
people on earth, Dan.
He senses our presence,
he keeps calculating
closer and closer.
- I don't believe that.
I am sure that I've asked
some other scientific minds
capability of a foil
to prevent detection.
- [Tom] Even worse actually.
- If you only
could find the way,
only one way of communication
with each other.
- Do you think we
still have a Garrison
on the space platform?
Roman hasn't destroyed that yet?
- Well, it could be, if he
only could get through to them,
but why should we succeed
where others failed?
- Don't you talk like that dear.
- [Joel] I have to talk
like that, I'm German.
(siren buzzes)
- [Tom] Excuse me, hey,
the cookies are done.
- This maybe them,
maybe they're coming
from the space platform.
- Humans, listen to me.
- [Crow] Okay.
- Due to an error
in calculation,
there are still a
few of you left.
- [Joel] We sincerely apologize
for any inconvenience.
that may have caused.
- Now, I know you all watching.
I see five of you who
have not been destroyed.
Show yourselves and I
promise you a painless death.
- [Tom] Yeah, we're looking
at a few other offers first.
- But this is incredible, it
means to droids stand too.
- I'll bet Alice is happy,
the way they used to fight.
- Hey, don't say that Johnny.
Joe was a great scientist.
- I wouldn't have never
developed a syrup without him.
- [Tom] Maple syrup.
- He wouldn't admit I
was good at my field.
Anyone who could
fix that fuse screen
after what that class did
too, it is better than good.
- Easy, easy.
- I'm sorry.
Seems silly after all
the terrible things
that have happened, to
go to pieces over one,
miserable, impossible guy.
- [Tom] Goodness, I love him.
He's a jerk, but he's my jerk.
- Do you wonder what
happened to your fellows?
Watch them.
- [Crow] They were forced to
watch boring war documentaries.
- [Joel] Hey my fellows
never looked liked buildings.
- I'm not watching that.
(upbeat music)
- Servo, Servo, come
in my faithful servant.
- I am here, your excellency.
- Why have not you killed human?
- Because it gives
me crunchy treats
and he empties my load pack.
- But he is human
and unfit to live.
- He's kind of cute.
He has good bone structure
and you can drive a stick.
- There is no room for your
petty sentimentality or your,
he can drive a stick?
Nevertheless, he is
human, kill him by sundown
or you will feel my wrath.
- Okay, I will try
but I do not think
he is going to like it much.
- You have the effrontery
to defy my orders?
- No, nothing like that, Sir.
I'm getting a call
on the other line,
I'm going to have to
put you on hold though,
Supreme being of the universe.
Oh, rats, I got to
shut this thing off.
- This is no party line dolt,
try to play telephone tag
with me, you will
clinker and clink ring
mishmash of guarded
Harley Davidson remnants.
Oh the earth man approaches
now, destroy him.
- No problem, I must destroy--
- Hey Crow, Tom
servo, what's up?
- Your number, I'm afraid.
I must kill you Mr. Bond,
I must kill you now.
- Joel, what happened?
- Tom Servo is, his reason
circus must have burnt out.
He tried to kill me.
- Oh no, Joel, we were just
doing a little role playing,
kill the human role
play like in the movie.
- Oh no, Tom Servo,
buddy, you gotta wake up.
- Oh, my aching cam's film.
- I'm sorry, Tom, I didn't
know you were kidding.
- Oh man, somebody must've
forgotten the robotic laws
of Isaac Asimov, I think.
- I know, I'm sorry, a robot
can never kill a human.
- Right.
- I'm really sorry.
What can I do to make
it up to you, Tom?
- You could let me kill you
Mr. Bone, you could let me--
- Oh, stop, he was kidding.
- Oh no, we got movies.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] I'm sorry, I didn't
know you were kidding.
- [Crow] I often do that,
I don't have a
breakaway body, Joel.
- [Tom] I thought it was cool.
- [Crow] Of course you did.
It's like their futon
survived the Holocaust.
- Are you there, anybody home?
- [Crow] Oh, their
survival clothing
must be getting
pretty gamey by now.
- Do you know who was in the
cave at the end of the ravine?
- Roman.
- Well, I was as close
to him as I am to you.
- So was I.
- But he didn't know
that I was there.
- Do you know why?
- Maybe not with noticing.
- Oh, now I know I'm
in the right house.
- Yes, and a moment
ago she was crying
because you went dead.
- You didn't have to waste
any tears on me, honey.
I bear a charmed life.
- [Tom] Served in the
Sheriff's department.
- (mumbles), he said that
we had the last five people
on the earth, is he lying
or are there any other?
- Two more, Jason and McLeod.
- But why then, that
doesn't make sense.
- Oh, doesn't it, look,
the professor here
spends his entire life
trying to discover a serum.
An antibiotic serum that
will cure all diseases,
even the common cold, and
thanks to his wife's choice
of assistance, he manages
to achieve his goal.
And so who does he experiment
on with his first injection?
- [Crow] Monkeys.
- Himself, his family,
myself and Jason and McLeod.
Therefore the great antibiotic
is also the immunizer
the Roman death trick.
- And I have follow up, it
will stay electronic Patty
can't around the house.
- Well, that may prevent
Roman from finding us
and blowing us up.
- Which is nothing.
- But against the sweep of
the death rate is powerless.
No, the serum, that's the thing.
- [Tom] Chocolate serum?
- Would you find
any more in the lab?
- Plenty, but I didn't bring it.
- Why?
- Because we managed to
get together enough fuel
to take a Rocketship
to the space platform.
- [Joel] Smart.
- There's enough serum
on board to immunize
the entire Garrison.
- Does he know you're coming?
- Well, how can I tell them
without letting Roman know too.
- They know what's
going on down here.
They'll figure it's
Roman and blast the ship
right out of the sky, you'll
have to get word to the space
that that's all.
- Jason and McLeod take
off in two days, on foot,
it would take me longer
than that to get back there.
- [Joel] Jason and
McLeaod (mumbles).
- You'll have to rewind the
circus on the view screen,
so that we can broadcast
without Roman picking it up.
- That's it.
- Such a complicated job
in two days.
- Well, at least I can try.
If I only had a decent
assistant who could take orders
instead of trying
to be the boss.
- I'm bossy, you're so
bossy, you ought to be milked
before you come home at night.
(murmurs)
- [Crow] I'll get
a stool on a pale.
- [Joel] That's
utterly ridiculous.
- [Crow] How could you say that?
- [Joel] Are you're going
about this for all it's worth.
- Don't you have to loop it.
- will you not argue, please!
- Looks like a steel powered
soldering wire.
- You something, you're either
too beautiful to be so smart
or too smart to be so beautiful.
- I guess we do get along
all right with that.
But let's work together
now, we can play later.
- [Joel] Some people
really have a strange idea
about foreplay.
- Well, what time is it?
- It's Miller time.
- What day, Roy?
- It's Miller day.
- I'm so tired.
There, there.
- Oh, Lord, we'll never make it.
I Can't control
my hands anymore.
- Let's rest a little.
- But we can't.
- No, he's right, it's
time you get some sleep.
- Surely, two days,
he's been at it.
- Oh, not that long,
it can't be that long.
- It is.
- The Rocketrip must
have taken off at dawn.
- Yeah, either they are by now.
- [Joel] Two darks, two
lights, that's two days failed.
- That's terrible,
I'm sorry, Dan.
- Do you realize what you
tried to do was impossible,
but you almost did it?
- But I didn't.
- That's why it's impossible.
- [Joel] Now this is what
Dr. Cornelius would look like
if he was played
by Raymond Berg.
- [Joel] You think of is
going to rule the world,
he'd pick a better
spot than a cave.
- [Tom] On the bus line.
- [Crow] And it's
a rent control.
- [Joel] Another
fireside chat with Roman.
- Now I find six.
- He still does know
about Jason and Macau.
- [Tom] Yeah, but
you just told him.
- There were eight of
you, the guidance, Roman,
who understands
everything showed me that.
And I might have had trouble
locating the other two
had they're not taken
off in a rocketship
and revealed their presence.
Look, humans.
(rocket engine roars)
- [Joel] Oh, it's
just a V2 rocket.
- [Tom] No, he
could have had a V8,
joke, joke, joke, sorry.
- [Joel] I thought
it was hilarious.
- I had it for the space,
which guidance Roman spared
because it would have been
a convenience for my people,
when they arrive on earth.
- [Tom] (laughs), look
at that, it's an power.
- Space platform.
- Now, we shall
destroy that too.
(rocket engine roars)
10, nine, eight--
- Seven (mumbles)
Hey, stay true to
your count down.
- [Tom] The guy
can just drop it.
- [Joel] That's a
Lucas effect, isn't it?
- [Crow] Buddy Lucas.
- [Tom] I just saw the hand.
- Seven and eight, all.
- [Joel] They look really bored,
you should them with a joke.
- I know, out of the two
billion, there're six.
Algenate your chances,
negative, negative,
negative, negative.
- [Tom] He's so negative.
- Is there a choice between
a painless surrender death
and the heart of
resistance death left?
- [Joel] No, I didn't know the
death rate had two settings.
- Y'all clock time in
one hour, I see you out.
Last warning.
- [Joel] The screen turned
back into her refrigerator.
- Mommy why doesn't
he like people?
- [Tom] He likes most people,
it's just you he hates.
- I don't know darling.
- He's not alone.
- It's best if we
can talk to him.
You better go and rest, do it.
- [Tom] He just got up.
- George, we can't go
on this way much longer.
Our food is almost gone.
- What else can we do?
Commit suicide or
give into Roman?
- [Tom] What was
the first one again?
- The last people on earth?
- Just talk to him, they can
see that we won't harm him.
He can let us live, if I
was going to finish rewiring
the viewer screen, you could
have talked to the platform
without Roman
discovering our presence.
- [Joel] But you didn't.
- Why don't you talk
directly to him?
- I could have,
of cause I could.
As soon as Alice, I
said sleep, I will.
(soft music)
- [Tom] What is this, a
shed Spread commercial?
- [Alice] Not like that.
- [Tom] Alice look, you
simply can't connect
these two circuits.
- [Alice] Here, let me.
- [Joel] Her hands
are sadly soft.
- [Tom] Hey, Roman
got a CD player.
- [Joel] And I think
there's a ham radio.
- [Crow] And a lunchbox.
- [Tom] Maybe it's a ham
and cheese radio, (laughs).
Hamman Cheese.
- [Joel] It looks like Gino
Vannelli with a kettle head.
- I thought I told you
to never call me here.
- Roman, do you scan
us your view screen?
- Yes, earth man, I see you.
This means only one thing
you have decided to take
the easy way out.
- No, Roman, we have
followed your a stand still.
And we will undoing it
as long as necessarily.
If you're trying to
figure out a position,
you are wasting your time.
- I'm going to
tell a scape lead.
I usually find no way to read
this earth planets of humans.
- No, we human will not
give up this earth of ours.
- [Joel] Never.
- But let me ask
you something else.
- [Tom] Have you thought about
your future, insurance needs?
- What do you
actually need from us?
Let me show you the sick
people you want to destroy.
- [Tom] Thanks, we've
been dying to meet them.
- First, my wife, Martha,
my companion for 23 years.
- [Crow] She bakes a strudel
that'll make you stand on that.
- Hear from this woman.
- The human is the
bringer human life,
and must be added to your race.
- Or my children, Alice.
- No, I have a mission I have
a mission to to kill them all.
- [Tom] Carla, she
can take a nothing day
and suddenly make
it all seem to work.
- And Shawnee.
- The boy is, or is it
in the entity called over
people, that children
must be murdered.
- You are not like my people,
you are Savage barbarians,
non-roman, animals.
- Take my assistant, Roy.
- [Tom And Crow] Please.
- Her lawyer developed
a serum with me,
which will test out
disease among my people.
- Wait.
- [Joel] what's my
line again, Oh yeah.
- There is something I
do not understand quite,
but I want to see
the girl Alice again.
- Okay, now tilt
the camera down.
- We want peace Roman,
but peace with honor.
- I will talk with a girl,
it is not in the plan,
but, although I
cannot verify it,
I feel that she will understand.
- No, I am the head
of this family unit.
You'll have to talk with me.
- Alkylate human, if
I meet with a girl,
I may find a way to
integrate you into the plan.
It is not a fact, what
you would call a hope.
- Name the place
Roman I will be there.
- I do not understand what it
is only the one called Alice
that I want to see.
- [Joel] For some reason, I
feel like calling you that now.
- Here I am Roman,
where should we meet?
- [Tom] And your high
school gym right after math.
- There is a rule in there,
I will meet you in an hour.
- I will be there.
- You're not going.
- I said get out of my way.
- And I said, you're
not coming here.
(Alice screams)
- [Joel] Oh, it's discipline
time, Johnny, go to your room.
Excuse me, pull my finger,
Pulled my own finger.
- [Tom] Hey, it's an
old film, a "Bigfoot."
- [Joel] Ooh, we should be one
of those operating vehicles,
I'm getting a little too
big to climb these planets.
- Johnny, Johnny,
Johnny is gone.
- You don't think he'd
be outside the back?
- Oh, that Roman kid
will try anything,
what a servant I have!
- I didn't anything.
- Johnny has left to the cave.
he might have it in
his hand to find Roman.
You have to stop him.
- Don't worry, professor,
Alice and I can find them.
- I'll go, of course, but
don't either of you speak.
- [Joel] Little boy who
crumbled the Roman Empire
- [Tom] And kill
the fatted calf.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] It's a good
clean Howard, I like that.
(murmurs)
- [Tom] I got the
eyebrows for it.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] What is Roman,
a parade of homes?
He's just roaming around.
- What are you doing here boy?
- My sister isn't coming.
- So they sent you?
- I came by myself,
I wanted to find out
what you had against me.
- [Joel] You're a
voice for starters.
- You're human, your people
were getting too intelligent.
We could not wait until you
were strong enough to attack us.
We had to attack you first.
- I think you're just a big
bully picking on people smarter
than you are.
- No, I will kill you.
- [Joel] Bad did it,
see he's a big bully.
- [Crow] Kill first
ask questions later.
- You look like a
pooped out pinwheel.
- [Joel] Oh, come here
and say that you kid.
- Really cannot harm you,
your father must be a
brilliant scientist.
- He's got a super
serum that keeps people
from ever getting sick.
- Maple syrup.
- How do you know it works?
- 'Cause he tried it on me,
Alice, Roy and everybody,
and we don't get
sick, 12 capsules
with real bed bugs in them.
- Maybe you should stop
eating bugs, anyway.
- And the two men
in the Rocketship,
they also had this injection?
- Sure they...
- Always singing
like a Canary.
- I will calculate
a spectrum dustin,
the counseling to death rate
to counteract this antibiotic.
- [Tom] And how do you
hear about my antibiotic?
Who was the uncle biotic
and other little Biotics.
- [Joel] The biotic man, come
back here you rotten kid.
I'm going to shake my
fist at you, oh boy.
- [Joel] What's so scary
about an alien that looks like
the mascot of a
college football team.
- [Crow] He must
be from Texas A&M,
Ape and Monster, (laughs).
- Oh, hit him.
- Oh, that didn't hurt.
- [Joel] It's really quite
nice when you get used to it.
The Hills are alive with
the sound of weird music.
- [Tom] Yeah, this is what
we've been waiting for.
Try to stay on
camera, everybody.
All right, she can
walk, but you can't run.
- [Crow] It's just
that her knees give up
when she sees a robot monster.
- [Joel] She can't eat, she
can't sleep, all she wants to do
is think about him, be
with him, groom him.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] No more static
out of you buddy.
- [Tom] Tuck down
here in the bunker.
It looks like a
walking paintbrush.
- [Joel] Well maybe he's from
that Sherwin Williams planet.
You know the one that's
covered with paint?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Stop beating
around the bush.
- [Joel] He kind of looks
like Baloo, the bear
of the "Jungle book,"
those ape necessities.
- [Tom] Robot
monster necessities.
- George, there you he is.
- Run, run.
- Shoot him a bunker.
- Come into the bunker.
- [Joel] You became one of them.
- [Tom] I was standing there.
- [Tom] Hey, you
bring the chips?
Where's the salsa, looks like
he spilled the sour cream.
- [Tom] Empty handed again,
always wipe your feet.
before I bring a bunker.
- It's all right, now
tell us all about it.
- No worries mom,
I gave it all away,
I didn't mean to, but I did.
- You did what?
- I wanted to talk to
Roman, but he got out of me,
however, protected
from the disarray
and not always going to
do something about it.
- [Joel] Now he's
going to sue us.
- You did right in the
Roman won't find it easy
to counteract to serum, so we
have still a little time left.
- [Joel] Butterscotch syrup?
- Now let's go over to Janie's
house and borrow her dogs?
- Yes, of course Sarah--
- You're one sick puppy, kid.
- [Crow] Shoulder flares
at the end of the earth.
Even at the end of the
world, love springs eternal,
man needs a woman to be his
steed, woman needs man, yeah.
Now she got the need.
- [Crow] Is that right, Joel?
- [Joel] I think it's
something like that.
It's all Alice Cooper song.
- [Tom] Hey, he's
bleeding from the ear.
- [Joel] Must be good.
- It's a little kids voice.
(soft music)
- [Tom] Give me some hearing.
Oh, he de-flowered her..
- [Joel] That's nothing,
see the sun honey up there,
way back that sun means
nothing, but you, you something.
Yeah, you are something girl.
- Yep, well, I feel
the same way about you,
your forehead and everything,
but it's gloomy and well,
wait a minute, you
are big whereas me,
well I'm small, yeah.
- [Crow] Oh honey,
you're my kind of gal.
Oh, huh, I missed that
Joel, that was beautiful.
- [Joel] I feel so real.
- [Crow] I feel used.
- [Joel] I feel you
I'm defenseless.
Yes, let's go to a commercial.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Here comes
Robin Rowdy Roman.
While mommy braided Cindy's
hair, daddy read from the home
repair and improvement
Bunker guide.
- We can put a
ceiling on this place.
- [Joel] Who's got the time,
it's the end of the earth.
There's always time
for a good roof.
- [Tom] Catch.
- What has kept you at a two?
- [Joel] What don't you know?
- Have you been house?
- [Tom] In a way, in a way.
- Professor, it may sound
silly to you, but Alice and I
want to get married, and we
were wondering how you'd feel
about performing the ceremony?
- You want me to?
- Oh, yes.
- In that's case, let's do it.
And I want you to know,
this is the biggest
social event of the year.
- [Tom] It's the only
social event of the year,
it's the last social event
of the year, we know,
- [Crow] Meanwhile
at the monkey house,
Ballou had just awakened
from a long winner's nap.
- [Tom] I just took a tick bath
and I can't do a
thing with this pal.
- [Joel] You think he's
going to get jealous
that Alice is going to get
married to another guy?
Only time will tell.
- [Crow] It's going to be
like the curly knife scene
in Oklahoma.
- [Joel] Come in same guy.
- Great guidance, I have
discovered the secret
of our failure to you have to
destroy the remaining human.
- [Joel] It's these gorilla
suits, they really slow me down.
- I want a sea Ray, the
calcium data death ray,
can not penetrate them,
they have been made immune
to the antibiotic syrup,
which I believe is the same as
our formula XZA.
- Or janitor at a drunk.
- Eliminating at all, that's
the humans and I fought.
- [Tom] Remember
your S training.
- The plan shall be fulfilled,
the planet earth app revolt.
You have other short
time to achieve our goal.
- [Joel] The pyramid
game of death.
(dramatic music)
We'll be right back after this
message from the Geritol law.
Really up to about half
a billion bubble so far
I've been counting.
- All right.
- Smiles everyone.
- [Tom] Hey, no shoes,
no shirt, no ceremony.
- [Joel] It's an
Armageddon wedding.
- [Crow] Armageddon getting
married in the morning.
- [Tom] Nice Oregon.
- [Crow] Gorilla, my dreams.
- Dear Lord, you know that I
am not trained for this job.
- [Tom] Acting, huh?
- But I have tried
to live by your laws,
the 10 commandments, if you
had to totes the golden rule.
- [Joel] The rule of emperor.
- Proportions you to look
down on Alice and try
and give you a blessing.
- And try not to spit.
- Because I'll be the
faith, in your grand design,
there may be no room
for a man's triumph
over this particular
evil that has beset us.
But if by any chance, victory
should be on our side.
I want you to give a long
flight to Alice and Roy,
and a fruitful one.
- [Joel] The last
couple on earth.
- Watch over them this night,
watch over us all, amen.
- Amen.
- And now, I pronounced
you man and wife.
Roy, do you have to the ring?
- I didn't think about that.
- Oh brother, are you going
to have to pick up after him?
- I wanted you to have
it someday, I promise.
- [Tom] I was going to sell
it, but everybody else's dead.
- With this ring, I do wed you.
And the only thing
to seal it now--
- [Tom] So is this movie
it's wed, wed, dead right?
- [Joel] And now if everyone
could go to the fellowship hall
for bars and punch.
- Where are you going on your
honey moon, I have a bus?
- Oh no, the forbidden zone,
we're just going to
bonk around for awhile.
We haven't thought about it.
- Wherever you go, be
careful, and I want you back
the first thing in the morning,
and in case you don't know,
you guys are all going to get
back, I don't want to give up.
- Thanks for everything, dad,
most of all for having raised
Alice, you too mom.
- I'll go get my
things, then we go.
- [Tom] What things
could you possibly have?
- [Crow] Her stick,
rather stick,
- [Joel] Man, somebody
has got to take that kid
out of the rain.
(dramatic music)
It's magilla gorilla
beacon through (mumbles).
- [Joel] It looks like he's
just going to break out and say
like 23 Skidoo any second.
- Someday, babe,
this'll all be yours.
- Roy, Alice, wait for me.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm getting your present.
- Oh you little rascle.
Thank you very much, now you
better run right at home.
- Faster, faster, hey and
home is the other way,
unless you want to go Roman.
- [Joel] Roman, oh, roman
outstanding in his field.
- [Tom] Oh, it's me.
Now, come back here,
I've got some etchings,
I'd love to show you.
- Never tell you about
the game against Stanford
back in 2013.
- [Crow] Lovely, lovely lady.
- What are doing here
alone girl child?
- My daddy won't
let you hurt me.
(murmurs)
(dramatic music)
- Oh, no, oh, Joel, I think
I'm having heart palpitations.
This movie is really
getting to me.
- Yeah, Joel, I think I'm
developing an aneurysm.
Please, no more movies.
- Come on, you guys aren't
supposed to have human ailments
besides I think
it's kind of cool
in a dark surrealistic
sort of way.
- So it standing in front
of a speeding snowmobile.
- No, you don't
get it, you see it.
Isn't it kind of weird,
it's like there's a guy
in a gorilla suit and
there's, he's got a robot head
and inside, he's got
kind of a bunch of clay.
I mean I've seen Dalai
paintings that make more sense
than this movie does.
- But I think there's a
fine line between surrealism
and costume shop close outs.
- I don't get it, Joel, is
it cool to make no sense?
- No.
- It's hip to be vague.
- It's not cool to make no
sense, but it's surreal.
- Oh, like dang strawberry
potatoes climbing Mount Everest
in tears.
- Right, you got it, right.
Look even the cam bots getting
into it with the monitor,
yeah.
- Oh, well, then I will follow
the dripping cows go Yugoslav
cap cutting and liter hosing.
- Right, is that
cool though, Joel?
- No, it's not Cool,
but it's surreal.
- It's kind of fun to
really think about it.
- Well, see you in the floating
head, Bantu peccadillo,
Mr. Macreet.
- Yeah, so tax, but dang, Whoa.
- My robots, I think I'll
crush grape jelly in my neck
and tell the clocks come home.
(upbeat music)
I need something sweet now,
a little boy would go
very nice right now.
Oh boy, this is Casey
case for America's top 40.
Our first letter comes
from Darley and rice Lake
who writes Casey.
(soft music)
What, what, if not one
thing, it's another.
I got to add a reason, these
legs, the size at cables,
I was in a shower,
what do you want?
- Great guidance, I have
already eliminated one of them.
- [Tom] sounds painful.
- Was a simple measure
of strangulation.
I believe five more and one more
on whom I have made an estimate
in relation to our strategic
reserve, the plan should
include one living human
for reference and
contingency plan,
do you question the plan?
- No, great one,
I only postulate.
Destroy the others, all of them.
- [Joel] Boy, I hate
talking to that guy.
I got an ulcer, the size of a
lap dog, and what does he do?
Keep talking and talking.
- [Tom] And when we go to see
the other three banana splits?
- [Joel] I'm going
to go push a crane.
- [Crow] Sorghum,
nature's rich bounty.
(soft music)
(dramatic music)
Pan, pan, pan, oh, we're going
to have to hose those two off
like the dogs in the yard.
- [Crow] What a
romantic honeymoon!
- [Joel] Right on the back 40.
- [Crow] I don't know if
they've gotten to that one yet.
He hates love.
(Alice screams)
- [Joel] Can't have
love, forbidden to love.
- [Tom] Run away.
- [Joel] Yeah, I saw
that coming a mile away.
- [Crow] One punched Larry.
(Alice screams)
- [Joel] That
ladies and gentlemen
is the destroyer of the
universe, I rest my case.
- [Crow] Pretty pathetic.
- [Tom] Bound to happen, I
got the girl, I got the girl.
That'd be squeezer, I
will call her toward.
- Hey, you two, my marriage
license has expired.
You're not really
married, come back.
- Oh.
- No, (Martha cries).
- He will hear you.
- I don't care.
- I can see lady.
- You must care, you
must not give up.
- [Tom] Hey, you might make
a better door and a window.
- [Crow] Has the Roman killed
like all the other wildlife
on the planet too, there's
no birds or anything.
- [Joel] Roman is just
filled with hate Tom servo.
I'm the only party farmer.
- [Tom] All right, beautiful
in the hands of hideous beast.
This is my kind of movie.
- [Joel] The miniature
version of King Kong.
- I must do it with my hands.
- It seems impossible.
- [Tom] Well, I try and
stay in shape, eat right.
- Individual energizers.
- Strong enough
to carry with you?
- No, mine is in the cave.
- I wish Mary played
house with me more often
when she wanted to.
- [Tom] Shut up you
little insensitive adult.
- We enjoyed those
lungs she wants with us.
And now somehow we have to
find a way to live without her.
- [Tom] Is this the
Donner party story?
- Yeah, Donna Reed, Oh, okay.
Oh, I did it again, sorry.
Match me up and
call me a potato.
- A robot, big robot
helmet, robot romance.
- [Joel] Starting out
of the grave dear.
- [Tom] Am I your
first bro, Man,
let me show you
what I've got done.
What I've done with the
cave is it's very romantic.
You're going to love it,
I got mirrors on this,
the leg tights and I
got a new CD player.
- And nothing can be done.
- Maybe one of us could
run him out for a moment,
and the others can
run in and get Alice.
- That's easier said than done.
- He'd come if he could
be sure of killing us.
- Go on, go on.
- Don't be bored.
- [Tom] I like him.
- I like the viewer
screen, tell him
we don't want to fight anymore,
he couldn't get a review
if he promises easy death.
- [Joel] And then
he kills us, right?
- You slip in and grab Alice
when he comes out after me.
- That's my plan,
there's no time to lose.
- [Joel] I like it.
Mother, keep digging
graves, better do two,
this isn't going to well,
- Little one, big one.
- [Tom] And I got the whole
cow sales collection on CD,
it's going to be great,
you're going to love it.
- [Joel] It's off of merchandise
well you've overgrown
dust, bunny.
(dramatic music)
- Suppose I were you human,
would you treat me like a man?
- [Joel] He's been
using the view screen.
Now cut that out, I
don't like alien types
touching our women folk.
That's it, that's it,
you come knocking.
- [Tom] Oh, no, he's fitting
her for a gorilla suit.
Girl, pop it.
- Ooh, nice tag.
- Nice swollen, nice fall.
- [Joel] Look, I'm
really busy right now,
if you can call back,
I'd really appreciate it.
- Why do you call
me at this time?
- Roman, we can't
stand it any longer.
- I have made my last offer.
- You will promise painless
death, if he can give ourselves,
come get us.
- You can wait, call me
again at another time.
- No.
- Kinda busy right now.
- We can meet halfway
into the review.
- All right, I will
lead you in the Ravine
when the sun passes
over the mountains.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Did she tie herself up?
Oh, what is it now?
Every time I find a earth girl,
I like, I get a phone call,
"Roman this, Roman that."
- Kill the human.
- Attention, extension XJ2.
- [Joel] Extension
attention extension XJ2.
- [Tom] Hey, I'm up to my
armpits and humans down here.
The painters are in, I can't
fill half these orders.
Look at me, I'm a wreck.
- You have captured the
girl and not destroyed her.
You have the lady accepting
the surrender of the others.
This verges on video.
There was one thing you
could not understand
great guidance, you
would reject the plan,
I wish to make an
estimate of my own.
- You think for yourself
to be like the human.
- Me man?
- Yes.
He liked the Human
to laugh, feel, want.
Why are these things
not in the plan?
- You are an extension
of the Roman and a Roman,
you will remain, now I
sent you into motion.
One, destroy the girl,
two, destroy the family.
Fail, and I will destroy you.
- [Tom] What's number
three, I get a choice?
- [Joel] Do not
violate (mumbles).
What a touching little scene!
- I cannot yet I must,
how do you calculate that?
At what point on the graph,
you must and cannot eat.
I must.
- But you cannot.
This guy's deep.
- That's a touching
soliloquy, deep and thick.
- [Crow] He's furry.
- [Joel] Now son, this is the
first thing time you've been
away from home during the
destroyer of the world,
out of his layer to save
what's left to mankind.
So I want you to keep a cheerful
disposition and remember to
wash up, and I want you to
take this hairdryer with you
for safekeeping, now
your mother and I
will get safely away from
the blast zone, really.
- [Tom] To get work, (laughs).
- Oh, what's that
kid going to do
with that their hot glue gun?
Stick the apes, pelt
that a cave wall?
(soft music)
- Attention extension XJ2.
- [Joel] Attention extension.
- [Tom] Put them on a call.
Ban ban ban.
- Speak great guidance.
- Why have you not
killed the girl?
- I must but I cannot.
- I couldn't kill her,
the cutaway to the
scene of the humans
and I can really
kill her on camera.
- [Tom] This monkey's in love.
- [Joel] And now I
have the girls tied up,
you're not going anywhere.
- I will kill the boy.
- Here I am.
- Alice, do not hate me, I must.
- [Joel] But it really
smells in that cave.
We can through the
knothole and grumbles.
- [Tom] I've hired an idiot.
- [Joel] Lovely, lovely.
- Wish to be a human, good,
you can die like human.
- Whoa.
- Whoa!
- [Joel] Well, same the suit.
At least it's rented.
- No.
(mumbles), I am the
ruler of all Roman.
- A different voice.
- [Tom] Cue the
Deus Ex-Mackinac.
- [Joel] Deus
Ex-Machina, isn't it?
- [Tom] You say Mac
Sheena, I say Makina.
- [Crow] Let's pause
the whole line off.
- [Tom] Katie.
- [Joel] It's a Plato
fun set come to life.
The magic of Claymation.
- [Tom] Triceratops.
- [Joel] Okay, but I
usually don't like ceratops.
- Vibrations will smash the
predator out of universe.
- [Tom] Oh, come
on, we've seen this.
- [Joel] Oh, oh.
- Oh.
It's get-go Roman wrestling.
(chuckles).
- [Joel] Yeah, turnover.
- [Crow] The most tastes
like chicken to each other.
- [Tom] Oh, that looks
real, that doesn't.
Must be pretty good
lizard glue they used
to put that fin on that Gator.
- [Tom] Aren't they supposed
to fight the humans?
- [Joel] No humans, this
is entirely different film.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] There goes the
Tyco railroad scenery.
- [Joel] It's sort of a shame
to see it break like that.
- What, how is he?
- He's all right.
We just want to make
sure that you get up
with everything
you fell down with.
- I found him next to
that flimsy plot device.
- [Tom] Yeah, I was
doing a beer bond
with the guys from theater K.
- Yeah, I found him.
- Oh, that's quite a
month, what happened?
- Darling, are you all right?
- You gave your
brother quite a scare.
- Yes.
- It's almost getting
dark and no Johnny.
- You're alive?
- [Tom] Mom I've turned Hindu.
- Why, was that a
dream or was it?
- [Tom And Crow] It was.
- Why don't you and your
assistant join us for dinner,
- Done.
- Did.
- Will you play house
with me hen we get home?
- [Joel] Yes, we'll play
house, for God's sake, shut up.
- All right, but I got
to keep an eye on Roman.
- It really Johnny you're
overdoing your space, man.
There's simply ain't
any such things.
- [Joel] Anybody
better my cleanings.
- [Tom] Can the Roman crap.
(soft music)
Is this the end
of the film, Joel?
- [Joel] No, I
don't think it is.
- [Crow] You got a day job.
- [Joel] What?
Oh, this is pathetic.
- [Tom] Gonna go puke.
(dramatic music)
- In honor of this week's
film being over with,
the robots and I have
organized a brief skit
titled, "Servo."
- The life and times of
Roman, the Roman pageant
are in search of the
historical robot monster.
- Fact, Roman, the Roman
destroyed almost all
of Earth's population
save for six refugees
yet they all lived within
a short walk of his cave.
- Fact Roman, the Roman is a
cosmic Ray that kept the cities
of the world in tack to be
enjoyed later by all Roman
yet he lived in a cave and
not even a very good cave.
- Yeah, yeah slack heat, oh.
Roman, the Roman
was an artificially
created being devoid of
any human passion, normal fears,
tenderness or forgiveness,
ultimately lacking that,
which mortals clink to most,
humanity yet he liked bubbles.
- Roman, the Roman came from
his civilization light years
ahead of earth's or at least
the earth portrayed in the film
yet he frequently gestured
like how I Mendell go figure.
- We believe these truths to
be self evident and obvious.
- Please give to the
United Robot college fund.
- Because an internal hard
drive is a terrible thing
to waste, think about
it, why don't you,
what do you think, sirs?
- Hmmmmmm.
- Could we have sent a
stranger person into space?
What in the name of
Jules Bergman was that?
- You think maybe he's
had enough of there?
I think he snapped.
By no means here, file this.
Well, until next
week jumpsuit Jolie.
(gentle ominous music)